Clark W. Thompson papers, Inclusive: 1931-1966, undated, Bulk: 1959-1966
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Committees, 1961-1966; 2
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce, 1963 May (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce, 1963 May-July (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce, 1963 August-September (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce, 1963 October-December (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce, 1964 January-March (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce, 1964 April-August (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Judiciary, General, 1964-1965 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Judiciary, Anti-Trust Matters (1 of 3), 1966 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Judiciary, Anti-Trust Matters (2 of 3), 1966 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Judiciary, Anti-Trust Matters (3 of 3), 1966 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Judiciary, Civil Rights (1 of 2), 1964-1965 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Judiciary, Civil Rights (2 of 2), 1964-1965 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Judiciary, Firearms (1 of 3), 1965 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Judiciary, Firearms (2 of 3), 1965 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Judiciary, Firearms (3 of 3), 1965 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Judiciary, Firearms, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Judiciary, Immigration to Naturalization, 1961-1964 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Judiciary, Immigration to Naturalization, 1965-1966 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Judiciary, School Prayer (1 of 4), 1964 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Judiciary, School Prayer (2 of 4), 1964 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Judiciary, School Prayer (3 of 4), 1964 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Judiciary, School Prayer (4 of 4), 1964 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Judiciary, Voting Rights, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries (1 of 2), 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries (2 of 2), 1963-1964 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries, 1965-1966 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Public Works, 1963-1964 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Post Office and Civil Service, General (1 of 5), 1963-1964 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Post Office and Civil Service, General (2 of 5), 1963-1964 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Post Office and Civil Service, General (3 of 5), 1963-1964 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Post Office and Civil Service, General (4 of 5), 1963-1964 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Post Office and Civil Service, General (5 of 5), 1963-1964 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Post Office and Civil Service, Pay and Benefits, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Public Works, 1965-1966 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Rules, 1962-1966 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Un-American Activities, 1963-1965 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Veterans Affairs (1 of 2), 1962-1964 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Veterans Affairs (2 of 2), 1962-1964 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Veterans Affairs, 1965-1966 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Ways and Means, General, 1962-1963 April (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Ways and Means, General, 1963 May-August (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Ways and Means, General, 1963 September-December (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Ways and Means, General, 1964 January-June (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Ways and Means, General, 1964 July-September (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Ways and Means, General, 1965 February-May (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Ways and Means, General, 1965 June-December (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Ways and Means, General, 1966 January-March (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Ways and Means, General, 1966 April-October (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Ways and Means, Cattle and Beef, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Ways and Means, Drugs, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Ways and Means, Finance, 1963-1964 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Ways and Means, Firearms, 1963-1965 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Ways and Means, Florence Agreement, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Ways and Means, H.R. 8282, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Ways and Means, H.R. 8282, 1966 January (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Ways and Means, H.R. 8282, 1966 February (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Ways and Means, H.R. 8282 (1 of 3), 1966 March (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Ways and Means, H.R. 8282 (2 of 3), 1966 March (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Ways and Means, H.R. 8282 (3 of 3), 1966 March (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Ways and Means, H.R. 8282 (1 of 2), 1966 April (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Ways and Means, H.R. 8282 (2 of 2), 1966 April (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Ways and Means, H.R. 8282, 1966 August (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Ways and Means, Medicare, 1963 April-August (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Ways and Means, Medicare, 1963 September-October (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Ways and Means, Medicare, 1963 November (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Ways and Means, Medicare, 1963 December (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Ways and Means, Medicare, 1964 January (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Ways and Means, Medicare (1 of 2), 1964 February (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Ways and Means, Medicare (2 of 2), 1964 February (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Ways and Means, Medicare, 1964 March (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Ways and Means, Medicare (1 of 2), 1964 April (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Ways and Means, Medicare (2 of 2), 1964 April (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Ways and Means, Medicare, 1964 May-June (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Ways and Means, Medicare, 1964 July-August (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Ways and Means, Medicare, 1964 September-December (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Ways and Means, Medicare, 1965 January (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Ways and Means, Medicare, 1965 February (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Ways and Means, Medicare (1 of 3), 1965 March (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Ways and Means, Medicare (2 of 3), 1965 March (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Ways and Means, Medicare (3 of 3), 1965 March (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Ways and Means, Medicare, 1965 April (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Ways and Means, Medicare, 1965 May-December (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Ways and Means, Medicare, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Ways and Means, Oil, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Ways and Means, Oil (1 of 5), 1963 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Ways and Means, Oil (2 of 5), 1963 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Ways and Means, Oil (3 of 5), 1963 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Ways and Means, Oil (4 of 5), 1963 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Ways and Means, Oil (5 of 5), 1963 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Ways and Means, Oil, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Ways and Means, Oil, 1965-1966 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Ways and Means, Social Security, General, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Ways and Means, Social Security, General, 1964-1966 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Ways and Means, Social Security, H.R. 15311, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Ways and Means, Social Security Tax on Tips, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Ways and Means, Tariffs and Trade (1 of 6), 1962-1965 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Ways and Means, Tariffs and Trade (2 of 6), 1962-1965 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Ways and Means, Tariffs and Trade (3 of 6), 1962-1965 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Ways and Means, Tariffs and Trade (4 of 6), 1962-1965 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Ways and Means, Tariffs and Trade (5 of 6), 1962-1965 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Ways and Means, Tariffs and Trade (6 of 6), 1962-1965 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Ways and Means, Tax, General (1 of 5), 1962-1966 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Ways and Means, Tax, General (2 of 5), 1962-1966 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Ways and Means, Tax, General (3 of 5), 1962-1966 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Ways and Means, Tax, General (4 of 5), 1962-1966 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Ways and Means, Tax, General (5 of 5), 1962-1966 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Ways and Means, Tax, Correspondence (1 of 7), 1963 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Ways and Means, Tax, Correspondence (2 of 7), 1963 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Ways and Means, Tax, Correspondence (3 of 7), 1963 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Ways and Means, Tax, Correspondence (4 of 7), 1963 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Ways and Means, Tax, Correspondence (5 of 7), 1963 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Ways and Means, Tax, Correspondence (6 of 7), 1963 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Ways and Means, Tax, Correspondence (7 of 7), 1963 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Ways and Means, Tax, Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Ways and Means, Tax, Correspondence, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Ways and Means, Tax, Correspondence (1 of 2), 1966 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Ways and Means, Tax, Correspondence (2 of 2), 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Ways and Means, Tax, Correspondence with Karl Bendersen, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Ways and Means, Tax, Excise Tax (1 of 5), 1963-1965 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Ways and Means, Tax, Excise Tax (2 of 5), 1963-1965 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Ways and Means, Tax, Excise Tax (3 of 5), 1963-1965 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Ways and Means, Tax, Excise Tax (4 of 5), 1963-1965 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Ways and Means, Tax, Excise Tax (5 of 5), 1963-1965 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Ways and Means, Tax, Hearing on Interest Equalization Tax Act, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1959-1966; 3
  This series contains correspondence from Clark Thompson’s legislative office. These letters deal with various political topics, including healthcare, firearms, and Civil Rights legislation from 1959 to 1966. Letters of a more personal nature are also included in the series but are far less common. Most of the correspondence is comprised of Thompson’s replies to letters, but a few of the original letters to Thompson are present as well. The series is in good condition.
  - Agriculture, 1963-1965 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Banking, 1963-1964 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Civil Defense, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Civil Rights, 1963-1966 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Civil Service Commission, 1963-1965 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Commerce, 1963-1964 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Communism, 1962-1963 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Congress, 1963-1965 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Education, 1963-1964 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Elections and Campaigns, 1962-1964 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Electricity, 1963-1966 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Employment, 1963-1964 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Environment, 1962-1965 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Equal Rights, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Federal Aviation Administration, 1963-1964 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1963-1964 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Food and Drug Administration, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Fishing, 1963-1964 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Foreign Affairs, 1963-1966 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Foreign Aid, 1963-1966 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Galveston, 1963-1965 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - General, 1963-1966 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Gun control, 1964-1966 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Healthcare, 1963-1965 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Housing, 1963-1965 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Immigration, 1963-1965 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Industry, 1963-1964 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Indian Affairs, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Insurance, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - International, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Interstate Commerce, 1963-1964 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Invitations, 1963-1964 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Judicial Committee, 1963-1966 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Labor, 1963-1965 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Legislation (1 of 2), 1963-1965 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Legislation (2 of 2), 1963-1965 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Metric System, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Military, 1963-1964 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Nuclear, 1963-1964 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Oil and Gas, 1963-1964 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Organizations, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Peace Corps, 1962-1964 (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Personal, 1963-1966 (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Political Opinions, 1963-1964 (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Post Office and Mail, 1963-1965 (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Poverty, 1964-1965 (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - Radio and Telephone, 1963-1964 (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - Railroad, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Redistricting, 1963-1965 (Box 28, Folder 45)
  - Religion, 1963-1964 (Box 28, Folder 46)
  - Responding to Complaints, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 47)
  - Retirement, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 48)
  - Rivers and Harbors, 1962-1966 (Box 28, Folder 49)
  - Small Business Administration, 1963-1964 (Box 28, Folder 50)
  - Social Security, 1963-1966 (Box 28, Folder 51)
  - Space and the National Aeronautics and Space Administration, 1963-1964 (Box 28, Folder 52)
  - State Department, 1963-1964 (Box 28, Folder 53)
  - Taxes, 1962-1966 (Box 28, Folder 54)
  - Transportation, 1963-1964 (Box 28, Folder 55)
  - Veterans, 1963-1965 (Box 28, Folder 56)
  - Ways and Means, 1963-1966 (Box 28, Folder 57)
  - Weather Bureau, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 58)
  - White House, 1963-1964 (Box 28, Folder 59)
- Departments, 1955-1966; 4
  Series IV. Departments deals primarily with executive departments. While the Agriculture, HEW (Health, Education, and Welfare), and Post Office Departments comprise most of the material, each of President Lyndon Johnson’s departments - apart from Transportation - are represented here. The series is mostly in alphabetical order and is in good condition.
  - Agriculture, General, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Agriculture, General, 1963 January-May (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Agriculture, General, 1963 June-July (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Agriculture, General, 1963 August-October (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Agriculture, General, 1963 November-December (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Agriculture, General, 1964 January-May (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Agriculture, General, 1964 June-September (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Agriculture, General, 1964 October-December (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Agriculture, General, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Agriculture, General, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Agriculture, Farmer’s Bulletin, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Agriculture, Agriculture Stabilization and Conservation Service, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Agriculture, Agriculture Stabilization and Conservation Service, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Agriculture, Agriculture Stabilization and Conservation Service, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Agriculture, Agriculture Stabilization and Conservation Service, 1965-1966 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Agriculture, Proposal for Farm Labor Housing, 1963 October (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Agriculture, Reference Book for Clark Thompson, 1966 October (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Agriculture, Rice, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Agriculture, Rice, 1961 January-March (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Agriculture, Rice, 1961 April-June (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Agriculture, Rice, 1961 July-December (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Agriculture, Rice, 1962 January-July (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Agriculture, Rice, 1962 August-December (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Agriculture, Rural Electrification Administration, 1959-1962 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Agriculture, Rural Electrification Administration, 1963-1964 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Agriculture, Rural Electrification Administration, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Agriculture, Rural Electrification Administration, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Agriculture, Soil Conservation Service, 1963 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Agriculture, Soil Conservation Service, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Agriculture, Soil Conservation Service, 1965 February-March (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Agriculture, Soil Conservation Service, 1965 April-1966 June (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Commerce, General, 1960-1961 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Commerce, General, 1962-1963 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Commerce, General, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Commerce, General, 1965-1966 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Commerce, Accelerated Public Works Projects, General, 1963 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Commerce, Accelerated Public Works Projects, Directory, 1963 August (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Commerce, Area Redevelopment Administration, 1961-1964 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Commerce, Bureau of Public Roads, 1960-1966 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Commerce, Census Bureau (1 of 2), 1959-1962 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Commerce, Census Bureau (2 of 2), 1959-1962 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Commerce, Census Bureau, 1962-1966 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Commerce, Lumber Standards, 1963-1964 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Commerce, Maritime Administration, 1965-1966 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Commerce, Weather Bureau (1 of 2), 1961-1964 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Commerce, Weather Bureau (2 of 2), 1961-1964 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Defense, General, 1960-1961 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Defense, Air Force, 1960-1962 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Defense, Army, General, 1965-1966 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Defense, Army, Cases, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Defense, Cases, 1959-1961 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Defense, Cases (1 of 2), 1961-1962 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Defense, Cases (2 of 2), 1961-1962 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Defense, Marine Corps, Cases, 1959-1962 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Defense, National Guard, 1960-1962 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Defense, Navy, General, 1961 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Defense, Navy, Cases, 1958-1962 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, General, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, General, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, General, 1961 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, General, 1962 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, General, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, General, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, General, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, General, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Cuban Refugee Program, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Food and Drug Administration, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Food and Drug Administration, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Food and Drug Administration, 1961-1962 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Food and Drug Administration, 1963-1964 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Food and Drug Administration, 1965-1966 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Handbook of Programs of the HEW Department, 1964-1965 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Migrant Health Service Program, 1964-1965 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Office of Education, General, 1959-1965 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Office of Education, General, 1965-1966 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Office of Education, National Defense Education Act, 1961-1966 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Office of Juvenile Delinquency and Youth Development, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Public Health Service, General, 1959-1965 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Public Health Service, General, 1965-1966 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Public Health Service Act, Amendment of Title VI, 1958-1966 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Public Health Service Act, Amendment of Title VII, 1963-1964 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Public Health Service Act, Cancer Research, 1961 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Public Health Service, Galveston Hospital Briefing Notebook, 1963 July (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Public Health Service, Closing of Galveston Hospital, 1963-1964 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Public Health Service, Closing of Galveston Hospital, 1965 January-February (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Public Health Service, Closing of Galveston Hospital, 1965 February-March (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Public Health Service, Closing of Galveston Hospital, 1965 March-July (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Public Health Service, Closing of Galveston Hospital, 1965-1966 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Public Health Service, Hospital Closures, General (1 of 2), 1965 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Public Health Service, Hospital Closures, General (2 of 2), 1965 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Public Health Service, Hospital Closures, Clippings, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Public Health Service, Report of the University of Texas Medical Branch at Galveston, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Public Health Service, Water Pollution, 1959-1965 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Social Security Administration, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Social Security Administration, 1962-1964 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Vocational Rehabilitation Administration, 1963-1966 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Welfare, 1964-1966 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Housing and Urban Development, General, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Housing and Urban Development, Federal Housing Administration, 1961-1962 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Housing and Urban Development, Federal Housing Administration, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Housing and Urban Development, Federal Housing Administration, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Interior, General, 1952-1962 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Interior, General, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Interior, General, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Interior, Bureau of Indian Affairs, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Interior, Bureau of Reclamation, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Interior, Bureau of Reclamation, 1963-1965 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Interior, Fish and Wildlife Service, 1959-1963 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Interior, Geological Survey, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Interior, Bureau of Land Management, 1959-1964 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Interior, National Park Service, 1963-1966 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Justice, 1959-1961 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Justice, 1962-1964 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Justice, 1965-1966 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Labor, General, 1960-1963 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Labor, General, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Labor, General (1 of 2), 1965 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Labor, General (2 of 2), 1965 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Labor, College Placement Activities, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Labor, Bureau of Employees’ Compensation, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Labor, National Labor Relations Board, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Labor, Neighborhood Youth Corps Program, 1965-1966 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Labor, Safety and Health Standards, 1963-1964 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Labor, Strikes, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Post Office, General, 1956-1958 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Post Office, General, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Post Office, General, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Post Office, General, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Post Office, General, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Post Office, General, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Post Office, General, 1964 January-March (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Post Office, General, 1964 April-December (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Post Office, General, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Post Office, General, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Post Office, Commemorative Stamps, 1955-1962 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Post Office, Census for Mailings (1 of 2), 1966 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Post Office, Census for Mailings (2 of 2), 1966 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Post Office, Anahuac, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Post Office, Angleton, 1961-1962 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Post Office, Algoa, Alvin and Arcadia, 1957-1962 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Post Office, Bauliff, Bloomington, and Boling, 1961-1963 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Post Office, Brazoria, Brookshire, and Bay City, 1960-1963 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Post Office, Clute, Columbus, Damon, and El Campo, 1958-1963 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Post Office, Fayetteville, Flatonia, Freeport, and Fulshear, 1961-1962 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Post Office, Galveston, 1964-1965 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Post Office, Ganado and Glen Fora, 1960-1963 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Post Office, Hallettsville and Hankamer, 1960-1962 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Post Office, Hempstead (1 of 2), 1961-1963 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Post Office, Hempstead (2 of 2), 1961-1963 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Post Office, Industry and Kemah, 1961-1963 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Post Office, Lake Jackson, La Marque, and League City, 1960-1962 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Post Office, Lolita, Long Mott, and Louise, 1960-1963 (Box 39, Folder 1)